Oh my god!
I have a very special guest today and a special video so you should check it out.
Today is all about body bags but not body bags for dead people but for having fun.
And since I can't show it to you alone I have help by the beautiful lady Elendor.
Hi!
Bright and shiny sent this along but they do not only make these in latex
they also sent something else. A spandex body bag and I think, let me check, this one also has a hood.
And we're going to show them to you. Very interesting. Have you worn something like this before?
No, it's my first time. Okay, I didn't either so we'll see how that goes.
One special thing here is that this latex body bag which we're going to try out first has a neck entry
which basically means you have to squeeze your whole body through this neck opening.
Did you wear a neck entry piece before?
No, it's also the first time.
Well lucky you, you're the winner today.
And in the feet part we have this kind of tunnel here for attaching a vacuum cleaner.
That will be fun.
Yes.
If you're wondering about her outfit, she just had a photoshoot and we thought why not
use it as an intro because it looks really good.
But unfortunately you have to get out of it now because again if you start with this I
will help you to get into it.
Alright, you changed.
Completely because you got rid of your wig and have different hair now.
And we have a bodysuit because it's safe for YouTube. Let's get started.
Since we're handling latex and lube, I guess we need a towel.
So you can step on that and lose your Christmas socks.
And foxes and Christmas trees.
Foxes and Christmas trees.
Alright.
Maybe you can also use your hands and like...
help yourself into it.
Oh, where are you? I don't know.
Thank you.
I think now you can stand up and stand on the feet.
I feel like we're getting somewhere at least.
Maybe like pull it over your butt first.
Now you look like a mermaid.
Just scream if you fall.
Now the arms.
Alright, you have to...
I'm trying, I'm trying!
Try it again.
Done!
bit not easy. Now you okay? Yes. Yes? Okay because I'm going to
shine it up a bit because now we have a lot of skin cells from getting into it here.
It looks like sleeping bags.
Do you think you can like maybe hop around so they can...
I can help your shoulders so you don't fall.
like all around so we can see the backside.
Ha!
Just like a little bunny.
Actually, I mean you can
hop around again so we can see your
beautiful face again.
Alright, now we have the
problem that
the vacuum
thing is right under your feet, right?
Yep. Okay, so...
Sit down please.
And now I need to get the vacuum cleaner.
Luckily I prepared something and have it here.
Alright let me check, because I have no idea.
Okay I managed to get it over the vacuum cleaner end and I hope it works this way.
Are you ready?
Yes.
You think so?
Okay, let's turn it on in three two one
Oh sorry you can't stand up anymore because we have the clamp here.
I'll let you down.
How do you feel?
It's a weird feeling.
But not so bad. Does it make like a huge difference now that we suck the air out of it?
Yeah, it's different. But good. Which one feels better?
I think this one. Yes? Yeah.
Can you still move your arms or anything? No. A little bit my finger.
Yeah.
That's all.
I mean, we can try to do it again and maybe then you can send up without the clamp.
All right, what I noticed is that I had to like pull the vacuum cleaner a bit away so
that the air can flow and I folded it into itself without a clamp so we can try if you
just stand on it that it will like still hold the air.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You're standing?
Yeah, I'm standing.
I'm gonna take your chair away.
All right.
Is it different standing up now?
A little bit.
Yeah.
It looks cool, like you can see the bodysuit beneath and the lines and everything and like the individual fingers
That is cool
Would you like can you imagine to do it to I don't know use it privately in your free time
Is it something that like appeals to you or?
Sure, I mean it feels really good
But to get inside
Yeah, you definitely need a second person
Yeah
This one is a standard size, but there's a made-to-measure option available. Also a lot of different colors.
Did you even like see yourself in the mirror yet? Yeah, I think it looks really good.
And since you can't really do anything now...
Aha!
All right, shall I release you?
Yes!
If I pull it away from here, basically I should get in. Oh, yeah.
Work really good. Yes. I think that's easier than trying to get it from the feet up. Yeah.
Okay, now I'll just have to pull it down again.
Yeah.
You made it out again.
Yay.
But since I don't want to be a bad host,
I will do it too, not with the latex one.
I'll get into the spandex.